{
  "type": "quiz",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "きゃ",
      "answer": "kya"
    },
    {
      "question": "きゅ",
      "answer": "kyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "きょ",
      "answer": "kyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "しゃ",
      "answer": "sha"
    },
    {
      "question": "しゅ",
      "answer": "shu"
    },
    {
      "question": "しょ",
      "answer": "sho"
    },
    {
      "question": "ちゃ",
      "answer": "cha"
    },
    {
      "question": "ちゅ",
      "answer": "chu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ちょ",
      "answer": "cho"
    },
    {
      "question": "にゃ",
      "answer": "nya"
    },
    {
      "question": "にゅ",
      "answer": "nyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "にょ",
      "answer": "nyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ひゃ",
      "answer": "hya"
    },
    {
      "question": "ひゅ",
      "answer": "hyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ひょ",
      "answer": "hyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "みゃ",
      "answer": "mya"
    },
    {
      "question": "みゅ",
      "answer": "myu"
    },
    {
      "question": "みょ",
      "answer": "myo"
    },
    {
      "question": "りゃ",
      "answer": "rya"
    },
    {
      "question": "りゅ",
      "answer": "ryu"
    },
    {
      "question": "りょ",
      "answer": "ryo"
    }
  ]
}
